<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Chenyen Lai</title>
    <link>http://chenyenlai.gitlab.io/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Chenyen Lai</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://chenyenlai.gitlab.io/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>http://chenyenlai.gitlab.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://chenyenlai.gitlab.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>Research Appointments  (2017-) Postdoctoral Associate
Theoretical division (T-4) and Center for integrated nanotechnologies
Los Alamos National Laboratory, Los Alamos NM 87545 USA
 (2014-2017) Postdoctoral Scholar
School of Natural Science
University of California, Merced, Merced CA 95340 USA
 (2008-2009) Research Assistance
Department of Physics
National Tsing Hua University, Hsinchu 30013 Taiwan
  Educations  (2009-2014) Doctor of Philosophy
Department of Physics
University of California, Riverside, Riverside CA 92521 USA</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>http://chenyenlai.gitlab.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://chenyenlai.gitlab.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>WIP 2 Chen-Yen Lai, S. A. Trugman, D. A. Yarotski, and Jian-Xin Zhu “Time-resolved Optical Absorption Spectroscopy in a Terahertz-driven Hybrid System of Plasmons and Excitons.”
In preparation.
1 Chen-Yen Lai and S. A. Trugman,
“Absence of diffusion and fractal geometry in Holstein model at high temperature.”
In preparation.
Preprint Peer-reviewed 18 Chen-Yen Lai and Jian-Xin Zhu,
“Ultrafast X-ray Absorption Spectroscopy of Strongly Sorrelated Systems: Core Hole Effect.”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conference</title>
      <link>http://chenyenlai.gitlab.io/conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://chenyenlai.gitlab.io/conference/</guid>
      <description>Future Conference  APS March Meeting, Denver CO, 2020  Talks (Bold face are invited)  “Ultrafast spectroscopy of strongly correlated systems.” (Poster)
Strongly Correlated Quantum Materials, Santa Fe NM, Apr 29, 2019.
 “Non-equilibrium dynamics of spin and charge correlation in strongly correlated systems from pump-probe spectroscopy.&amp;rdquo;
APS March Meeting, Boston MA, Mar 6, 2019.
 “Microscopic dynamics in the Holstein model at high temperature: Absence of diffusion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collaborators</title>
      <link>http://chenyenlai.gitlab.io/collaborators/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://chenyenlai.gitlab.io/collaborators/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Jian-Xin Zhu Los Alamos National Laboratory
Dr. Stuart A. Trugman Los Alamos National Laboratory
Dr. Jhih-Shih You The Leibniz Institute for Solid State and Materials Research
Prof. Chih-Chun Chien University of California, Merced
Dr. Mekena Metcalf Lawrence Berkeley National Laboratory
Prof. Massimiliano Di Ventra University of California, San Diego
Prof. Michael Scheibner University of California, Merced
Prof. Shan-Wen Tsai University of California, Riverside
Prof. Yannick Meurice University of Iowa</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MISC</title>
      <link>http://chenyenlai.gitlab.io/misc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://chenyenlai.gitlab.io/misc/</guid>
      <description>Photography One of my long term habits since my childhood. Most of my work are on natural scene and wild animals. If you are interested, please pay a visit to my flickr page
Hiking Downhill Skiing I learned how to ski on 2016-17 winter with my son (he was 4 years old) at Ski China Peak. I admit that I am a slow learner on this (Yes, I fall all the time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>