<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Chen-Yen Lai</title>
    <link>http://chenyenlai.gitlab.io/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Chen-Yen Lai</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://chenyenlai.gitlab.io/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>http://chenyenlai.gitlab.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://chenyenlai.gitlab.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>Research Appointments  (2017-) Postdoctoral Associate
Theoretical division (T-4) and Center for integrated nanotechnologies
Los Alamos National Laboratory, Los Alamos, NM 87545 USA
 (2014-2017) Postdoctoral Scholar
School of Natural Science
University of California, Merced, Merced CA 95340 USA
 (2008-2009) Research Assistance Department of Physics
National Tsing Hua University, Hsinchu 30013 Taiwan
  Educations  (2009-2014) Doctor of Philosophy
Department of Physics
University of California, Riverside, Riverside CA 92521 USA</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>http://chenyenlai.gitlab.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://chenyenlai.gitlab.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>WIP 2 Chen-Yen Laiand Jian-Xin Zhu,
“Time-resolved X-ray absorption spectrascopy of strongly correlated systems: core hole effect.”
In preparation
1 Chen-Yen Lai and S. A. Trugman,
“Charge pumping, circulating current and fractal geometry in strong coupling Holstein model at high temperature”
In preparation.
Preprint 3 Mekena Metcalf, Chen-Yen Lai, Massimiliano Di Ventra and Chih-Chun Chien,
“Many-body multi-valuedness of particle-current variance in closed and open cold-atom systems”
arXiv:1805.06443 submitted to Phys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conference</title>
      <link>http://chenyenlai.gitlab.io/conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://chenyenlai.gitlab.io/conference/</guid>
      <description>Future Conference  APS March Meeting, Denver CO, 2020 APS March Meeting, Boston MA, 2019 APS Four Corners Section, Salt Lake City UT, 2018  Talks (Bold face are invited)  “Dynamics of Hostein model in strong coupling and high temperature: charge pumping and localization.”
BLABS, Theoretical Division, Los Alamos National Laboratory, May 21, 2018.
 “Time-resolved X-ray Spectroscopy in One-dimensional Strongly Correlated Systems.”
APS March Meeting, Los Angeles CA, 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collaborators</title>
      <link>http://chenyenlai.gitlab.io/collaborators/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://chenyenlai.gitlab.io/collaborators/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Jian-Xin Zhu Los Alamos National Laboratory
Dr. Stuart A. Trugman Los Alamos National Laboratory
Dr. Jhih-Shih You The Leibniz Institute for Solid State and Materials Research
Prof. Chih-Chun Chien University of California, Merced
Dr. Mekena Metcalf Sandia National Laboratory
Prof. Massimiliano Di Ventra University of California, San Diego
Prof. Michael Scheibner University of California, Merced
Prof. Shan-Wen Tsai University of California, Riverside
Prof. Yannick Meurice University of Iowa</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>